

Jet Hu Web Developer

20412-427-865

⊠hujienanmoon@gmail.com

github.com/hujienan

PROFILE

As a highly-motivated, enthusiastic and responsible person who had 3 years' web development experience, I love to study new technique, and I am keen on taking challenges. I just settled in Perth after my graduation from China, if you can supply a suitable job to me, I will do my best for my employer.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.),

Software Engineering

Aug 2013 - June 2017

Heilongjiang University

WORK EXPERIENCE

PHP Web Development Intern

Hangzhou, China

May 2016 - Oct 2016

Hithink RoyalFlush Information Network Co., Ltd

- Application comments' key words monitoring web project.
- Backend advertisements configuration web project.
- Stock information dynamic analyse project.

Team Leader & Frontend Developer

Harbin, China

Mar 2015 - May 2016

JR Tech Co. Ltd

- Leading to accomplish Construction managing system.
- Products presentation web project.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript jQuery Vue.js
 AngularJS Bootstrap Bulma Git Webpack
- PHP Laravel Smarty MySQL Node.js

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Primary School Teacher

Mar 2014 - Apr 2015

Young Volunteer Association of Heilongjiang University

Helped the students from remote villages to get more knowledge about universe, computer, and cross-culture beyond their textbooks.

INTRAMURAL AWARDS

- Excellent Student Cadre Dec 2014 & Dec 2015
- The Second Prize Scholarship Oct 2014 & Oct 2015
- Third Prize of Campus Mathematical Modeling Contest

- May 2015

Third Prize of Campus Program Design Contest

 $-May\ 2015$

Advanced Individual in Social *Practice* – Oct 2014